SANDRA SASU OTENG

P. O. Box KF 190,

Koforidua-Eastern Region, Ghana

+233 549652143

E-mail: sandyqe1300@gmail.com

Date of birth: 23rd April, 1990

Gender: Female

Marital status: Single

Religion: Christianity

Nationality: Ghanaian

Languages

spoken: English (Fluent), Twi (Mother tongue)

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am a vibrant and enthusiastic person, who is willing to contribute immensely towards the goals of your organization whilst acquiring much knowledge and diversified skills in an environment that offers greater challenge and good practical opportunities to help further my experience and knowledge to help the organization and the world as well in any good way.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND/ DURATION

ALL NATIONS UNIVERSITY COLLEGE, KOFORIDUA: 2013-2017

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), Accounting option

SAP TRAINING CERTIFICATION: NOVEMBER, 2015

SAP Business One [Logistics & Accounting], 4-week Training

AGONA NSABA SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL, AGONA NSABA: 2007-2011

West African Senior School Certificate Examination (Accounting)

SAINT GERMAIN SCHOOL COMPLEX, AGONA SWEDRU: 2004-2007

Basic Education Certificate Examination (BECE)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Currently working with the Ghana Health Service at Koforidua Polyclinic as a Nabco government contract staff. I work under the direct supervision of the chief accountant as a revenue collector for the Polyclinic in Koforidua Municipality.

I am currently a contract staff at Koforidua Polyclinic as a cashier after the Nabco contract ended. I assisted in the preparation of the Bank Statement affairs of Koforidua polyclinic, Auditing of the cashier's cash books and ledger entries were daily routine.

From August 2018 to October 2018: worked as a contract staff at the Ghana Revenue Authority, Koforidua, and Eastern Region of Ghana.

From September 2017 to July 2018: National Service Personnel at Ghana Revenue Authority, Koforidua branch, Eastern Region of Ghana.

From December 2011 to January 2012: worked as a Data Entry at Donkey Arts Enterprise, Elubo, Western Region of Ghana.

Responsibilities

- Updating taxpayers' files and keeping records on the various payments made. Such payments include withholding tax, Pay-As-You-Earn, Company tax and Personal Income Tax.
- Issuing of tax Credit Certificate to taxpayers after their settlement of withholding tax.
- Preparation of weekly, monthly and yearly reports on the office activities.
- Generating TIN (Taxpayer Identification Number) for taxpayers.
- De-registration of Taxpayers who have double TIN.
- Updating Taxpayers TIN information.

SKILLS / ABILITIES

- Proven ability to work under pressure, effectively.
- Professional and friendly client service.
- Possess personal and interpersonal skills.
- Adequate communication skills, both verbal and written.

- Good analytical and observational skills.
- High proficiency in Microsoft Office Suit

HOBBIES

- Reading, e.g. The Bible
- Dancing
- Cooking (Local dish)

REFERENCES

Mrs. Rashida Tegah

Principal Revenue Officer

Ghana Revenue Authority

Kaneshie Medium Taxpayers Office

Mobile Number: 0244563600

Mr. Samuel Kwasi Wiafe

Senior Revenue Officer

Ghana Revenue Authority

Koforidua Medium Taxpayers Office

Mobile Number: 0547543333, 0208801106

Mr. Stephen Owusu Mensah

Head of Accounts Unit

Koforidua Polyclinic

Mobile Number: 0570666649

Mr. Joseph Darkwah

Head of Accounting Department

All Nations University College

Mobile Number: 0208336993

Mr. Shadrack Cudjoe

Assistant Manager

Donkey Arts Enterprise, Elubo

Mobile Number: 0241301414